# Kelli Uyeda

kelli@uyeda.me | (626) 641-2379 | South Pasadena, CA https://uyeda.me | linkedin.com/in/kelli-uyeda | github.com/kellikells

## **Full-Stack Web Developer**

College graduate with a bachelor's degree in English, and more recently completed UCLA Extension Coding Bootcamp. Leveraging a background in hospitality to coalesce and build a more intuitive user experience on the web. Known for abilities to problem solve, meet deadlines, and be a successful team player.

### **Team-Based Projects:**

**Iphy Weather:** Focused on the use of API resources. Primary focused on back-end development to create a web application that provides the user with weather information based on location. Added user's ability to search weather conditions by *zipcode* or *city&state*. Successfully completed the project working with a team of 4 members in 12 days.

**Five Star Foodies:** Implemented MVC design pattern to build a restaurant search engine utilizing YelpAPI . Worked with another team member to incorporate secure user authentication through Auth0 alongside React.js and Node.js.

#### **Education**

University of California Los Angeles Extension - Coding Bootcamp University of California Los Angeles - Bachelor of Arts in English

## **Technology Summary**

ES6 JavaScript | TypeScript | React | JSX | jQuery | HTML5 | CSS | Tailwind CSS

Python | Java | Node.is

Express.js | Django | Flask

AWS | Vercel | Heroku | Git

SQL | MongoDB | Contentful | Firebase

Windows | Mac

### **Work Experience**

Freelance Full Stack Developer

Los Angeles, CA 2019-Present

**Dan Modern Chinese Restaurant** 

Pasadena, CA 2018-2019

Gyu Kaku Japanese BBQ

Pasadena, CA 2014-2018